<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Yicheng Huang</title>
    <link>https://yichenghuang980.github.io/data_science_portfolio/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Yicheng Huang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yichenghuang980.github.io/data_science_portfolio/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Estimate Effectiveness of Opioids Control Policies on Drug Overdose Mortality</title>
      <link>https://yichenghuang980.github.io/data_science_portfolio/projects/opioid/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yichenghuang980.github.io/data_science_portfolio/projects/opioid/</guid>
      <description>Over the past two decades, the United States has seen a tremendous increase in the use and abuse of prescription opioids, leading not only to a huge rise in opioid addiction, but also a rise in prescription overdose deaths, and increasingly deaths from non-prescription opioids like heroin and fentanyl as people who became addicted to opioids due to prescriptions turn to illegal markets to sustain their addiction.
In order to deal with those situations, several states that had notoriety for having high opioids prescriptions and overdose mortality issued their own policies in different years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Compare Fake News Detection Performance with Glove and Word2Vec Embedding in Keras</title>
      <link>https://yichenghuang980.github.io/data_science_portfolio/projects/fakenews/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yichenghuang980.github.io/data_science_portfolio/projects/fakenews/</guid>
      <description>While the pensioner of Ghent and his eminence were exchanging very low bows and a few words in voices still lower, a man of lofty stature, with a large face and broad shoulders, presented himself, in order to enter abreast with Guillaume Rym; one would have pronounced him a bull-dog by the side of a fox. His felt doublet and leather jerkin made a spot on the velvet and silk which surrounded him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Predict Transportation Challenges with Logistic Regression and RandomForest</title>
      <link>https://yichenghuang980.github.io/data_science_portfolio/projects/humana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yichenghuang980.github.io/data_science_portfolio/projects/humana/</guid>
      <description>With the rapid pace of social development, we humans have enjoyed an easier way of living and commuting. Meanwhile, we are exposed to a growing number of health-threatening substances and sites, which makes it harder for the medicare industry to evaluate health and its cost. Fortunately, the introduction of Humana’s integrated value-based health ecosystem based on Social Determinants of Health brings a promising prospect to this industry.
Among all those challenges to health, transportation challenge stands out to be the most common one since it involves daily life of a person’s commuting, schooling, and living.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Price Prediction inside AWS Serverless Data Engineering Pipeline</title>
      <link>https://yichenghuang980.github.io/data_science_portfolio/projects/bitcoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yichenghuang980.github.io/data_science_portfolio/projects/bitcoin/</guid>
      <description>Nevertheless, as be harangued them, the satisfaction and admiration unanimously excited by his costume were dissipated by his words; and when he reached that untoward conclusion: “As soon as his illustrious eminence, the cardinal, arrives, we will begin,” his voice was drowned in a thunder of hooting.
“Begin instantly! The mystery! the mystery immediately!” shrieked the people. And above all the voices, that of Johannes de Molendino was audible, piercing the uproar like the fife’s derisive serenade: “Commence instantly!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Operational Recommendations with SQL for Food Trucks during Music Festivals</title>
      <link>https://yichenghuang980.github.io/data_science_portfolio/projects/foodtruck/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yichenghuang980.github.io/data_science_portfolio/projects/foodtruck/</guid>
      <description>Poor Gringoire! the din of all the great double petards of the Saint-Jean, the discharge of twenty arquebuses on supports, the detonation of that famous serpentine of the Tower of Billy, which, during the siege of Paris, on Sunday, the twenty-sixth of September, 1465, killed seven Burgundians at one blow, the explosion of all the powder stored at the gate of the Temple, would have rent his ears less rudely at that solemn and dramatic moment, than these few words, which fell from the lips of the usher, “His eminence, Monseigneur the Cardinal de Bourbon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Continuous Delivery of Flask App Application via GCP</title>
      <link>https://yichenghuang980.github.io/data_science_portfolio/projects/flaskapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yichenghuang980.github.io/data_science_portfolio/projects/flaskapp/</guid>
      <description>Three hundred and forty-eight years, six months, and nineteen days ago to-day, the Parisians awoke to the sound of all the bells in the triple circuit of the city, the university, and the town ringing a full peal.
The sixth of January, 1482, is not, however, a day of which history has preserved the memory. There was nothing notable in the event which thus set the bells and the bourgeois of Paris in a ferment from early morning.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
